I'm analyzing why Richard's V-135 policy keeps winning.
And here's where my hypothesis on the strategy is.
So I think that Richard's policy,
they basically, they play, they basically,
they team up, and then they hover around this area,
right over here. and, you know, and the former.
group and then they basically circle around the base right over here, you know, towards
the letter part of the game, they circle around the base and they try to find like ways in
and so if they if they basically team up as four or five players, they're very strong
and especially when we're spread out, they have a much easier time to to form up and attack and then to
and you can and you know go.
with all their strengths.
I think there's a lot to be said by forming up as a team.
No splitting up when it's time,
they all come together in order to make a final attack.